

MAHSHID GHAFFARI

Front End Developer

- mahshid.info
- @ mahshid2ghaffari@gmail.com
- in mahshid-ghaffari-838949b7
- +31687153781mahshidghaffari
- Maastricht / Rotterdam

MY WORKS

Please visit my portfolio at mahshid.info

SKILL

JavaScript TypeScript

Vue/Nuxt.js | Vuex |

Composition API

React Axios HTML

CSS SPA PWA

Responsive Design

Bootstrap Vue

Element UI Web Pack

Java Docker GIT

Agile

ABOUT ME

A 4 years experienced Front-End Developer with a solid foundation in front-end development and a history of collaboration with renowned companies like Huawei and Ericsson. Holding a BSc in Data Science and Artificial Intelligence, a comprehensive skill set in web development, with a primary focus on Vue, Nuxt, and React. Crafting interactive, responsive websites for all displays is my forte, employing CSS and animation libraries such as Lottie. Proficiency in JavaScript and TypeScript is complemented by adeptness in Git and Docker for collaborative development. Additional expertise extends to the integration of Machine Learning with web analytics.

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

- Collaborated with APG Company to combine machine learning with Google Analytics data, resulting in the prediction of user dropouts and significant improvements to website UI/UX.
- Optimize stock and inventory management systems, resulting in streamlined processes and improved efficiency for Dutch Beauty Group.
- Conceptualized and developed an internal HR system for Eghtesaad-e Bidaar Brokerage, leading to enhanced payroll management and improved employee satisfaction.

LANGUAGES

Persian: Native

English: Fluent

Dutch: Basic / A2

EXPERIENCE

Front End developer | React | SteelTrace

iii Jan 2023 - Present

Maastricht , Netherland

- Spearheaded the debugging and optimization of the existing codebase, resulting in significantly enhanced performance and a seamless user experience utilizing React.
- Successfully refactored and streamlined the codebase, establishing a robust foundation for improved maintainability and scalability.
- Demonstrated expertise in developing reusable React components, contributing to faster loading speeds and efficient code maintenance.
- Collaborated closely with the development team to implement best practices, ensuring a high-quality and user-centric application.

Front End Developer | Vue | Nuxt | Dutch Beauty Group

iii Oct 2020 - Sep 2022

- Eindhoven , Netherland
- Designed and implemented advanced features, including dynamic table filtering, pagination, and URL-based filter preservation with Vue/Nuxt, resulting in a significant improvement in user experience, functionality, and loading speed.
- Developed reusable React components to enable efficient filtering, sorting, and file uploader validation, providing warehouse employees with enhanced productivity tools and streamlining inventory management processes.

Front End Developer | Eghtesaad-e Bidaar Brokerage

Mar 2018 - May 2020

- Tehran, Iran
- Revamped the stock and inventory management system using Vue JS, Leveraging microservices deployed within Docker containers with a PHP backend.
- Implemented data input forms for registering new buyers and sellers using Vue and Bootstrap-Vue.
- Implement a library "Form validator", and use lottie to create interactive animation with user.
- Created a Single Page Application for the company blog (Nuxt) to enhance advertising efforts.
- Developed an internal HR system for payroll, leave, and attendance using AngularJS.

EDUCATION

Bsc Data science and Artificial intelligence | Maastricht University

2023 - June 2023

- Maastricht, Netherlands
- Data Science and Machine Learning: Python, Natural Language Processing, Spacy, Machine Learning, Pandas, NumPy, Data Visualization, Data Preprocessing, R, Neural Networks
- Computer Science and Technologies: Data Structures and Algorithms, Java, MySQL, Matlab, Docker, GIT, Agile Methodologies, Cloud Computing (AWS, Azure, Google Cloud Platform)
- Mathematics and Analytic: Data Analysis, Numerical Mathematics, Probability and Statistics, Semantic Web (RDF, OWL, SPARQL)

Bachelor of Engineering, Urban Planning | Azad University

2010 - 2014

Tehran, Iran

Diploma of Math and Physics | 13 Aban High school

Tehran, Iran

HONERS

Winner of the Nokhbegan Math Olympiad (Calculus)

2010

Tehran, Iran

Winner of the Nokhbeegan Math Olympiad (Linear Algebra)

2010

Tehran, Iran